{
  "questions": {
    "multiQuestions": [
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is a Family Type?",
        "answer": "Instance types that have similar hardware specifications (CPU, vRAM, etc)",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is a security group?",
        "answer": "An instance level firewall allowing you to restrict Ingress and Egress traffic by specifying what traffic is allowed to communicate with that instance",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are some options of a Security Group to restrict inbound and outbound communication to an EC2 instance?",
        "answer": "Source, Ports, and Protocols",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What protocols are supported by ALB?",
        "answer": "HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, SMTP, and NFS",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "TCP, TLS, UDP, TCP_UDP"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What protocols are supported by NLB?",
        "answer": "TCP, TLS, UDP, TCP_UDP",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, SMTP, and NFS"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Elastic Load Balancer (ELB) balances traffic to a(n)",
        "answer": "Target Group",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "AutoScaling Group"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "EC2 Auto Scaling scales instances inside of a(n)",
        "answer": "AutoScaling Group",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "Target Group"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "When ALB uses HTTPS, what is the type of server certificate used?",
        "answer": "X.509 certificate",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "X.510 certificate",
          "X.409 certificate",
          "X.601 certificate"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is Cross-Zone Load Balancing?",
        "answer": "A setting for ELB. When enabled, ELBs will distribute traffic to targets across AZs evenly",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "For Lambda, which policy determines what resources the function has access to while running?",
        "answer": "Role Excecution Policies",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "Function Policy"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "For Lambda, which policy determines which AWS resources are allowed to invoke your function?",
        "answer": "Function Policy",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "Role Excecution Policies"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is needed for your Lambda to communicate with AWS services within your VPC?",
        "answer": "You need to toggle a setting in Lambda. And then give the Lambda additional execution roles (ec2:CreateNetworkInterface, ec2:DescribeNetworkInterfaces, ec2:DeleteNetworkInterface) so that it can give resources in your VPC, ENIs (Elastic Network Interfaces), and the lambda will need to be attached to a private subnet, with an optional NAT Gateway to access public internet",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is Unreserved Concurrency?",
        "answer": "How many functions can be ran at the same time within a single region. By default it is 1,000",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is Reserved Concurrency?",
        "answer": "You can reserve, say, 50 functions, and now the Unreserved pool of functions is only 950",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "How many functions can be ran at the same time within a single region. By default it is 1,000"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What happens when you Throttle a Lambda?",
        "answer": "Sets Reserved Concurrency of that function to 0. Meaning nothing can call it until you increase its Reserved Concurrency again to something greater than 0",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is an Event Source?",
        "answer": "The AWS Service that produces the event and triggers your Lambda",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "How do you get an instance to run terminal commands during its first boot cycle?",
        "answer": "Add the command to User Data",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is an Invocation Type?",
        "answer": "If the Lambda event is synchrounous or asynchrounous",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "A Reserved Instance can only be reserved for what timeframe?",
        "answer": "1 or 3 years",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "1 or 4 years",
          "1 or 2 years",
          "3 or 5 years"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is the difference between a Reserved Instance and a Scheduled Instance?",
        "answer": "A Reserved Instance is used for a specific length of time, whereas a Scheduled Instance boots up at a specific time and then shuts back down",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "A Reserved Instance boots up at a specific time and then shuts back down, whereas a Scheduled Instance is used for a specific length of time",
          "They are the same, but a Scheduled Instance is cheaper"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What does the ELB do to an EC2 instance when it fails a health check?",
        "answer": "Removes it from the Target Group and stops sending it traffic",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "Destroys it and creates a new EC2 instance",
          "Removes it from the AutoScaling group"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What does the EC2 AutoScaler do to an EC2 instance when it fails a health check?",
        "answer": "Destroys it and creates a new EC2 instance",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "Removes it from the Target Group"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Which type of Elastic Load Balancer support is ideal for receiving inbound traffic from the clients outside the VPC, offers TLS termination, and advanced routing?",
        "answer": "ALB",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "NLB",
          "Classic Load Balancer",
          "ELB"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "booleanQuestions": [
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "If an EC2 instance is stopped or terminated, ephemoral storage is lost",
        "answer": "True",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "If an EC2 instance is rebooted, ephemoral storage is lost",
        "answer": "False",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "For a Reserved Instance, it is cheaper to pay Partial Upfront than All Upfront",
        "answer": "False",
        "popup": "It is better to pay All Upfront, sometimes up to 75% off! It is most expensive to pay nothing before use. Partial Upfront is in the middle pricing wise",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "By default, AWS Lambda encrypts your environment variables *after* the function has been deployed",
        "answer": "True",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "By default, Lambda can access services in your VPC",
        "answer": "False",
        "popup": "By default, Lambda can only access resources via the internet (such as S3)",
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "When Lambda fails to handle a Synchronous Event, it will automatically retry the event 2 more times",
        "answer": "False",
        "popup": "The source sending the Synchronous Event is responsible for retrying. Lambda will only retry *Asynchronous Events* 2 more times",
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "For Lambda, poll based events are always synchrounous",
        "answer": "True",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Lambda is Serverless, event driven, and is cost affective",
        "answer": "True",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Key Pairs are used for connecting to EC2 instances, IAM, and other AWS resources",
        "answer": "False",
        "popup": "Key Pairs are only used for connecting to EC2 instances",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "When referencing ELB, you should use its static host name (url). Not its underlying IP Address",
        "answer": "True",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "An EBS volume is an example of ephemoral storage for an EC2 instance",
        "answer": "False",
        "popup": "An EBS volume is an example of persistent storage",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "An EBS volume will maintain its data when disconnected from an EC2 instance",
        "answer": "True",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "By default, data in an EBS Volume is backed up automatically to another EBS Volume within the same AZ",
        "answer": "True",
        "popup": "",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "checkboxQuestions": [
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "An Instance Type consists of what paremeters?",
        "answers": [
          "vCPUs",
          "Memory",
          "Instance Storage",
          "Network Performance"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are some options to get an AMI (Amazon Machine Image)?",
        "answers": [
          "Create your own",
          "AWS Marketplace",
          "Community AMIs"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are the different GLB types?",
        "answers": [
          "ALB",
          "NLB",
          "Classic Load Balancer"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Name the different Family Types",
        "answers": [
          "Micro Instances",
          "General Purpose",
          "Compute Optimized",
          "GPU Instances",
          "FPGA Instances",
          "Memory Optimized",
          "Storage Optimized"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Which of these are some Instance Purchasing Options for EC2?",
        "answers": [
          "On-Demand Instances",
          "Reserved Instances",
          "Scheduled Instances",
          "Spot Instances",
          "On-Demand Capacity Reservations"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is needed for your Lambda to communicate with AWS services within your VPC?",
        "answers": [
          "A setting in Lambda needs to be enabled",
          "Additional execution roles (ec2:CreateNetworkInterface, ec2:DescribeNetworkInterfaces, ec2:DeleteNetworkInterface) so that Lambda can give AWS resources in your VPC ENIs (Elastic Network Interfaces)",
          "Needs to be placed on a Private Subnet within the VPC (and given a NAT Gateway if it wants to speak to the public internet)"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "Needs to be placed on a Public Subnet within the VPC (and given a NAT Gateway if it wants to speak to the public internet)",
          "Additional Function roles (ec2:CreateNetworkInterface, ec2:DescribeNetworkInterfaces, ec2:DeleteNetworkInterface) so that Lambda can give AWS resources in your VPC ENIs (Elastic Network Interfaces)"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are the different Tenacity options?",
        "answers": [
          "Shared Tenancy",
          "Dedicated Instances",
          "Dedicated Hosts / Dedicated Host Instances"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [
        ],
        "tags": [
          "Lambda"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}